Hello friends, once again a very warm welcome to all of you
at Arvind Reading Service. Friends, today we are going to talk
about Indian Railways.
Friends, these days the shares of Indian Railways are
in huge profit and everyone involved in it has
made a lot of money. Friends, today we
will talk about its entire portfolio
and will tell you what its current price will be,
what will be the upcoming price, what will be the stop loss,
what is its market cap.
If you also want to know about all these things, then
like this video of ours and
watch it from beginning to end.
Friends, if you do not have a trading account, then
quickly go to my description and you
can open your demat account there for free. Friends, if
you want to join our Telegram channel, there is a
link in the description and you
can join for free. I
provide daily Android calls for free.
Friends, now let's go and take a look at Indian Railways
and learn
about it. Okay, friends, its
market cap is 52 thousand seven hundred twenty crores.
This company's current price is very high.
395  This is amazing, this is a
great price, this will be called, look
here, hydro has made 3425, that is, from 34 here it has
again made 3250, this company is
doing retracement here, there is a
very strong possibility of going up again from here,
I will try to explain it well where I will show you the chart,
friends, you can see its PM here, it
is 196, book bear 90157, David is also the company, there is
0.5% increase, that is 16.50, this is 11.6, face
value is 1.0, friends, now let's talk
about its chart, what does the chart do,
from where do we have to take stoploss,
friends, here I will
try to show you the chart, here I am
presenting you the chart of the novel,
friends, you will be able to see that 1 year
ago this company's share price was 13,
okay, today how much is 33 square 3296, it is not that it is
completing a lot of improvement, just
look at the fast August, 23
August 2002, till whom  25 were already 2533 fennel, which
means that a lot of improvement is to be
seen in IRCTC. As
our railways becomes stronger,
its price will increase. For a few days,
people thought that due to this, there was a slight
improvement in it because the
operation of all trains was stopped. But
now all the trains are
running well and the benefits are
happening in a very good way because here
you can estimate the price. But 395 is the
maximum price. If we look at it, you can
calculate the maximum price here like this. The maximum price here is
3295. Okay, this means that this is our high. The
company is doing a little treatment before last year. You have to be a little careful about this retracement.
This company will come down a bit. Here, after going into a slump, it is almost there. So,
you can see that from here, some
retracement comes like this, the company comes down. The
market does not go up at once, it will go down
again. Now, from here,
as soon as this cross the 3000 level, it goes down a little.  If it
comes around 1000
then you can take entry in it, your
target would have been 4505 D but the target would have been
friends, if you like this
video, please like the video friends,
how did you like our today's video,
please press the comment, friends,
we will try to know a little about its profit and loss,
we will see the profit and loss hydraulic net profit here,
you can see the company's second 97
crore 190 513, the people had a
good loop but still it is getting a little
better now, friends,
you can see the operating profit here, its a little
very good, after 190 it is 346,
method 703 D but in between there was a
little problem due to the people, there is improvement due to this officer, with
this the company is improving friends,
how did you like this video, let us know by commenting
with new videos, till then
thank you very much to all of you, Jai